Good morning everyone. I am Janina
Estates, head of investor relations of
Banko de Brazilio. Welcome to our live
streaming on the results of the first
quarter of 2023. Our event is in
Portuguese with simultaneous translation
into English. To choose the language,
click in the icon on the right side of
the screen and select the language of
your choice. To start, our CEO Tarcia
Medus and Joanni Tobia is our CFO. We
present the results of our performance
and at the end we will have a Q&A
session. We would like to remind the
analysts that questions can only be
asked using the webcast link. Also here
with us today is our VP for internal
control and risk management, Philippe
Prince. I will now turn the floor to our
CEO, Tarciana, to begin the
presentation. Good morning
everyone. I would like to to thank the
presence of analysts and shareholders
during this streaming to talk about our
manage management performance in the
first quarter of 2023. The profit of 8.5
billions accounts for a growth of
28.9% when compared to the same period
of last year. This performance shows our
commitment to sustainable business
generation and the efficiency in running
the company. The result that we
presented was based on the growth of
qual credit and the acceleration of our
digital transformation. With these two
lines of action, we went to increasingly
evolve in the delivery of a bank to
Brazil for each client. Always supported
by the disciplined execution of our
strategic
planning. Our loan portfolio grew in a
qualified way and exceeded the 1
trillion BRL mark for individuals,
corporations, family farming, agri
business and also for governments. We
posted significant performance in all
segments and we will continue to grow as
indicated in our
guidance. Digital transformation and
analytical intelligence allow us to be
more assertive in the credit offer at
Bankod Brazil. Credit quality and
digital transformation have drivers to
ensure that both are even closer and
more aligned to promote new businesses
and enable a long-term relationship with
our
clients. The use of digital tools is
becoming more and more pervasive in our
organization. We believe that in order
to be increasingly digital, we have to
go beyond what we already do very
successful, which is to be where our
clients are. This is critical for BB's
competitiveness and for the satisfaction
of our
customers. But we want a lot more and we
will not stop there. We want digital to
be the main driver for improving our
organizational culture and the strategic
decisions we make. This means having a
bank in which the use of data and
analytical intelligent are capable of
personalizing their relationship with
with clients. My mantra is to have a BB
for every client. We work with
hyperpersonalization to deliver
solutions that maximize our client
success. Knowing our clientele is a
lesson that I have carried with me since
my days as a farmers market seller. And
here at the bank, we have the ability to
get to know each of our millions of
clients in order to perform in a
relevant and close manner with
excellence. Excellence in relationship.
And I value this very much. The
employees of Banko Brazil carry in their
DNA the granting of credit as a means of
stimulating the country's development
and improving people's lives. In every
region of this country, Brazilians know
they can count on one of our employees
to offer them the best financial
solution. This large team of 85,000
people works in an organizational
environment where the values of the
digital world such as agility,
readiness, and assertive assertiveness
have gained ground. Additionally, the
use of analytical intelligence has been
important to our success to expand our
loan portfolio by 16.8% in 12 months.
Our NPL level is in line with our
expectations and below the average of
the national financial system.
I strongly believe that one of the
greatest assets of any business is the
efficient use of data and it couldn't be
different in the financial system. For
bankod Brazil, this is a reality. The
transformation that takes place every
day in our company makes Bankco Brazil
increasingly innovative. For us, the
physical and the digital are
complimementaryary and coexist for the
benefit of the client.
We do not let go of human close and
personalized contact. My legacy will be
the transformation of this immense
amount of data we have into an
exponential capacity to offer
personalized solutions to clients
wherever and whenever they need us. BB
holds an outstanding position and has
all the necessary conditions to grow
even more because it is a bank with a
strong connection to the Brazilian
economy. We have a technological
infrastructure that processes an average
of 16 billion financial transactions a
day, allowing us to obtain data from the
most diverse segments of our society,
consolidating our leadership position in
data processing in the financial
system. This gives us unique information
about the behavior of Brazilians. A
curious comparison that draws the
attention is that in the same 9.58
seconds that using bolt set the world
record for the 100 meter relay bank
Brazil processes 4,000 picks setting a
record in the financial system. We are
agile, modern and digital. In the first
quarter of this year alone, we total 705
billion BRLs in pigs transactions, up
52% compared to the first quarter of
2022. Millions of Brazilians use the
bank to send money via PICSS and each
one of these transactions adds more data
to our analytical models. All these
operations and the number of financial
transactions allow us to capture 500
million pieces of data from clients and
non-clients. This enables us to provide
more than 110 million personalized
offers on products and services. With
all this information, we can pinpoint
areas of the country where consumption
is higher and where the Brazilian
economy is more dynamic. We are able to
identify behaviors with a higher
profitability of consuming our
products and
also analyze people's payment capacity
with greater precision.
In summary, the biggest winners are our
clients who have financial products and
services that are more in line with
their consumption profile, thus
generating more sustainable businesses.
By the way, I will bring here more
numbers that confirm our commitment to
the financial sustainability of our
clients. We enable new businesses
through artificial intelligent solutions
such as Mingas Finances, a solution
available in our app that provides
financial education to our clients.
Since its launch, Mingas Finances had
already has already reached more than 4
million unique users and offered
1,400,000 financial plans with the use
of artificial intelligence to provide
our clients with a more prosperous
financial life.
What I showed a while ago shows how our
employees use all this data capture and
analytical intelligence to ensure that
these assets are at the service of the
country's development and of improving
people's lives. This is the art that we
perform every day here at the bank and
that's what makes us unique in the
financial system because we are able to
cons to combine our commercial
performance with our public function. We
know very well how to be a unique bank
with its own way of doing things. We
give adequate returns to our
shareholders and seek to meet society's
expectations in the construction of a
country that needs to create the
necessary conditions for improving
people's quality of life. This
commitment is very clear when we see
that we maintain our leadership in
payroll loans in the first quarter of
2023, increasing the number of people
served by this line. It was a 40%
growth totaling 700,000 clients served.
In this first quarter, we dispersed 3.1
billion bure in payroll loans to
beneficiaries of the INSS, which means a
79% increase when compared to the same
period of last year.
At Pronaf, we disperse 4.3 billion BRLs
to small farmers, up 38% compared to the
first quarter of
2022. There were more than 68,000
transactions representing an increase of
23%. Currently, 68% of BB's rural
transactions are related to family
agriculture.
I want to highlight that we work closely
with the small farmers and all the agra
business segments both inside and
outside the farm gate. Agra business is
and will always be strategic for banko
de Brazil. Therefore, we reaffirm our
commitment to stand by the Brazilian
rural grower in all sizes and in all
regions of the country. We are leaders
in the segment of the economy and we
want to be even more relevant.
The numbers show the importance we give
to our partnership with agri business.
In the current crop season, we have
already dispersed more than 148 billion
bure a 30% growth over the previous crop
year. In terms of our support to micro,
small and mediumsiz companies, we grew
24.2% in only one year, reaching a total
portfolio balance of 114.8 8 billion BL
supporting more than 135,000 companies
in this segment. Through Pronumpia
alone, we dispersed 2.4 billion BLS in
the first quarter of this year. The
segment of the economy is essential to
maintain and create jobs. But this is
not the only reason why we are
supporting the segment. We also support
it because the lines of prepayment of
receivables and working capital are
profitable for us and we are committed
to lending with a rigorous
approach to to lend with a rigorous
approach in our risk and credit
analysis. Being close to small farmers,
individuals and micro and small
companies also makes perfect sense to
us. Also when we think about the product
productive chain that we support uh our
model supports clients in a very broad
sense. We have also expanded our support
and funding to large infrastructure
projects and their value chains
especially those with ESG attributes
reaffirming our status as a relationship
bank for large corporations as well. In
this sense, we work at all stages of the
value chain in various sectors of the
economy. For example, we finance the
small farmer who produces milk and this
input will go to the dairy industry to
which we will offer a credit line and
solutions in capital markets. We also
understand the commercial rel
relationship between the various players
in a chain as a possibility for new
business and for promoting productive
activity. We are able to finance such
different and wide ranging sectors of
the economy because we have a very
strong capital structure sustained by
the adequate return and quality of the
funds we
lend. A fundamental attribute adds to
all our performance in favor of the
country. It is worth mentioning that
BB's performance generated 21 billion
bureaus of return to society in the
first quarter of this year in the form
of dividends, tax
payments, payments to suppliers and
payment of salaries among others.
Besides the direct return of its
performance, BB is increasingly present
in themes related to the ESG agenda. Our
sustainable business portfolio reached
328 billion bureels in Q1 up 13% over
the same period last
year. We have also encouraged female
entrepreneurship. Bangod Brazil
increased by 36% the volume of
dispersements to companies led by women
in this in this first quarter.
Internally in BB, the cause of
diversity, equity, and inclusion is
gaining more and more space with
concrete measures. For the first time in
our history, we have four women in our
board of directors in a totality in a
totally equal relationship. The board of
officers also has four women in its
composition.
almost half of the members of this
collegiate body and of these two are
self-declared members of the
LGBTQIAPN plus
group. In addition, BB created the
strategic committee of diversity,
equity, and inclusion. And here I
highlight the importance of this measure
due to its strategic position in the
company's governance. This committee
will have the same level of
deliberations and hierarchy as other
committees that are essential for the
bank's performance such as the credit
risk and capital committees. I also
emphasized that the number of jobs for
people with disabilities was increased
to
825 in our last public examination to be
admitted at the bank. In this final part
of my speech, I emphasized that Badu
Brazil's profit will be proportional to
our ability to create business. As our
guidance indicates, we will continue
growing in
2023. We want to continue to post
sustainable levels of profitability,
adequately remunerating the trust of our
shareholders. With a strong bank, we
will also create value for society as a
whole, granting quality credit to the
various sectors of the Brazilian economy
and offering excellent service to our
customers. We reaffirm the willingness
of bank Brazil to trust in the company's
economy and to believe in the capacity
of
Brazilians. BB will continue supporting
the economic and social development of
our society with financial solutions
that materialize in a more promising
reality for our country. Thank you very
much. I now turn the floor to our CFO
Giovanni.
We apologize but we are not getting the
sound. Please hold. We are not getting
the sound to
translate. Good morning one and all.
Thank you. Let me start by bringing on
the highlights of
Q123 results. Our numbers show a very
robust operating performance.
Undoubtedly in the year or near
comparison which mitigates seasonality
effects, we can see that growth of NI
and revenue from services fee income
more than offset increase in
administrative expenses and a triple L
expended view. With this we posted
income of 8.5 billion bureaus and a
return on equity of
21%. The loan portfolio expanded view
improved
16.8%. And the next slide please. In
comparison to March
2022, a positive performance in all
segments. The individual's portfolio
grew
11.7% in one year. And I would like to
call your attention to the volume of
operations to this segment. And I draw
your attention even more to payroll
loans that totaled 118.6 billion bure
corresponding to 40% of the individual's
portfolio. BB is the leader in this
market with a 20% share. The agra
business portfolio was definitely a
highlight in this quarter.
322.5 billion
BRLs up 4.1% quarter on quarter and up
26.7%
yearonear reflecting BB's leading
presence with all the clients in this
chain. This allowed us to recover our
market share. The proceeds that go to
sustainable agriculture represent almost
half of this portfolio.
The micro small and mediumsiz
enterprises portfolio reached 114.8
billion bureels growing 24.2% in 12
months. And here the highlight goes to
pronio operations. As Tari
mentioned, loans to large corporates
totaled 195 billion bure and annual
growth of 11.2% 2% with a highlight
going to private securities and
guarantees which rose 14.6% in 12
months. Moving to the next slide please.
Here we have our AL expanded view. It
was down
10.4% quarter on quarter. However, there
is one specific case in the last quarter
that explains this change. But compared
with the same period of last
year, it showed strong growth. The
result of the growth of our portfolio
and and yes, there was an increase in
the volume of provisions respecting the
quality of our
portfolio. I would also like to talk
about the provisioning in this quarter.
The variations in the Ale expenses,
credit risk and
impairment were affected by one specific
case. And it is important to stress that
there was no positive or negative impact
on the result linked to this negotiation
that happened and that led to a
restructuring of the debt that was a
credit and became a private security.
because of this rearrangement there was
this change and this is an operation
that was totally provisioned for and the
court supervised reorganization was
approved back in 2019. All
right.
Now, let's look at credit recovery. I
draw your attention to the volume of
credit recovery. 1.9 billion BRL when
compared quarteron quarter and year on
year. It becomes clear that we need to
tighten things a little more and advance
during the year in recovery to help us
uh maintain the risk of our portfolio.
Moving to the next slide please.
We would like to
mention would like to talk about credit
quality. We see that the delinquency
rates at BDO Brazil has been increasing
ending March 2023 at 2.62%.
quarter on quarter it is kind of
flat but there was increase compared to
March 2022 linked to the scenario that
we are living with a worsening of risk
overall but I would like to highlight
that the quality the credit quality of
the portfolio is uh above the Brazilian
financial
system and I would like to draw your
attention to our credit risk which is
below the Brazilian financial system.
Given the mix of our portfolio, we
continue to grow the individual's
portfolio, agri business portfolio,
corporates, agri business practically on
the right upper side of the slide has
remained stable.
However, we see an increase in
individual in companies delinquency
given the closing of capital
markets to companies refinancing with
private securities. And in the
individuals segment we believe that we
have achieved
uh the worst uh part of the the the
worst the the worst worsening of the
portfolio. We continue to present a
coverage
ratio superior to the system. We the
coverage ratio stood at
22.7%. And looking at the new NPO, we
believe that there is a small
impact the results of that specific case
that I spoke about earlier. But if we
look at the coverage of new NPL with
provisions, it would be around
87%. We had 7.4 4 billion
bure with a new NPL in Q1 2023. Now
moving to the next slide we'll speak a
little about net interest income
NI it ended Q123 with 21.2 billion
barrels, a rise of
38% compared to first quarter
22. Compared to Q422, we remained
practically flat. And I draw your
attention to the growth in Q1 because it
results basically from a funding
strategy that privileged the growth of
time deposits to help us fund the growth
of our credit portfolio.
credit uh
operation revenues highlight we can see
here 35% increase in the last 12 months
and 2.4% 4% in the last
quarter. This by virtue of the agra
business and individual loans and theme
loans. The growth of our funding
expenses 52% is the result of the
current scenario with the increase in
interest rates the cost of money cost of
capital. Our treasury results draw our
attention. It is to be highlighted.
It reflects our change in the mix of our
funding. Privileging some types of
funding lines to fund the expansion of
our loan book funding expenses always
also reflect the interest rates of the
country. Now moving to the next
slide talking a little bit about the
other components of our results. We
maintained proximity with our clients.
We fee the income grew just over 8% in
relation to Q122 totaling 8.1 billion of
bureaus. Uh and net of the seasonal
effect compared to Q4 there was a slight
decrease but that is linked to
seasonality. And I would like to
highlight administrative expenses. We
were able to maintain effective control
over our administrative expenses.
Personnel expenses followed. Salary
adjustments are given to the category of
our workers last year. But other
administrative expenses were very much
under control, even lower than in Q4 and
slightly higher than the same period
last year. All of that led bankod Brazil
to achieve the best cost to income ratio
in our historical series reaching
29%. On the next
slide, we present the uh common equity
tier one robust result. It allowed us to
main well our robust results allowed us
to keep common equity tier one stable
compared to December 2022 despite the
increase in our loan portfolio and loan
the loan book
increase. Uh we we believe that a bezel
ratio of 16.9% gives us comfort to
continue to support our relentless
execution of our strategy of being close
to our customers, creating sustainable
results and to continue to help
resilience realize their dreams by
financing all sectors of our nation.
Well, then I would like to end the
presentation talking a little about our
guidance. You can clearly see that well,
we are still at the very beginning, but
we keep to the commitment of executing
our strategy of delivering our guidance
of
2023. Individual loan portfolio growing.
We have organic growth and some
acquisition of portfolio which allowed
us to be at the top of the
range. Uh companies we grew above the
range but the trend is that it will be
between 7 and 11% growth for 2023. The
focus here is greater expansion inmemes
and our great business was definitely a
growth highlight above the range. It is
an industry that has been increasing
competitiveness a lot. Bankodu Brazil
there's a lot of competition but bankodu
Brazil is taking initiatives to recover
our market share. We are leaders but we
want to recover our market share and
postgrowth above the guidance but during
the year we believe that we will be
within the
range and it was still too early to look
at this and compare it but the trend is
by virtue of seasonality and change in
the mix of funding that we had along
2022 compared to Q1 2022 when we did not
have this new strategy. Well, it gave us
a result way above the range but during
the year will be between 17 and 21%.
Atria pol expanded view. We are hitting
the risk of credit. We have a challenge
of increasing credit recovery
and diligently controlling portfolio
risk. We grew a lot in the less risky
lines and that explains our new P&L that
is lower with less need of
provisioning fee
income performed in line with the
guidance administrative expenses as well
and net
income with annualization. We are in the
middle of the range. So confirming the
guidance for 2023 based on what we've
seen in Q1. I'd like to thank you for
your attention and I'd like to open the
floor to questions. Thank you very
much. Thank you Tiona. Thank you. We'll
begin now the Q&A
session. Questions may be asked in
Portuguese or English and we will answer
them in Portuguese.
We ask participants to ask just one
question so that we can give an
opportunity for all to ask. First
question from Bernardo Goodman with XP.
Bernardo, go
ahead. Good morning. Congratulations on
the results and thank you for taking my
question. Actually, I have two
questions. The first about the guidance.
you are at the top of the range in the
main metrics as Giovanni mentioned and
in that
regard does it make
sense for us to expect an upward
revision of the guidance because
historically numbers in Q2 and Q4 tend
to be stronger or maintaining the
guidance should mean an indication that
you're expecting a possible slowdown
looking forward in second question if
possible To coa, you completed 100 days
in office. Currently, the bank is in a
privileged position in different metrics
such as portfolio quality, control of
delinquency, capital level that is
deleveraged and very comfortable and
that translates into a very high ROE
with record marks. But historically
there was always a concern by investors
regarding political interference at the
bank. So to that end if we would
appreciate if this could tell us about
governance and how the institution is
advancing in that agenda because there
are demands from the new government and
differentiated risk execution that this
management has achieved in recent
quarters. Those are my questions. Thank
you very much.
Well, thank you very much for your
question. I will start answering the
second
question regarding governance of
Bankadoo
Brazil. We have a strong governance
structure with decisions that are taken
in a colleate manner.
There is no
pressure on the
bank to act with business lines that
will not bring adequate results for the
business. Recently uh just earlier in
the press conference I spoke about this.
We do not see any
room to operate with a credit policy
that is not technical.
or with credit policies
uh that would not fit bank Brazil's
credit policies. So we are very
confident that we have autonomy in
managing bank Brazil.
We will definitely take this
forward. Always developing business and
granting loans. Taking into account our
governance structure in our decision
making and developing products that will
bring us adequate return with a fair
counterpart based on our technical
analysis and supported by them.
So if I can answer the question about
the guidance. Bernardo, thank you for
the
question. We like to be
conservative. It is important to say
that undoubtedly we are relentless in a
disciplined execution of our strategy.
But
also we have the knowledge and we know
how the environment still requires
caution and prudence. We're a bank. We
are responsible for capital allocation
capital that is trusted by our
shareholders to us. We have robust
evaluation tools for our portfolio. We
know that particularly in large
corporates in the the with the private
securities market practically closed and
with the large corporates using
mechanisms of funding using private
securities. Well, so we have to be
attentive to that. Undoubtedly, agree
business is
uh a market that we expect to be uh
present with the share the bankio
deserves in that business. But like I
said, in terms of recovery, we need to
broaden our efforts even further in our
network so that we can increase credit
recovery.
Like I said,
we we have to be diligent regarding a
triple L. But when we look at the mix of
our portfolio, we still have a large
concentration, a large share of payroll
loans, which is an individual loan
category that has guarantees. It's much
lower
risk. If we look at its
performance, we even have this data. We
grew a share of double A from 14.8 to
19.2% in the individual's portfolio.
16.6A risk to
23.2%. In other words, we have less
provisions because we have this mix.
However, we we have to pay
attention. Why aren't we making
adjustments to the guidance? No problem
if we have to adjust the guidance upward
or downward. But it is still too early
to talk to talk about a guidance that we
have just communicated to the market and
again it reflects our strategy and this
is what we're going to
pursue. Excellent. Thank you for the
answers and Jovanni. Have a great
day. Our next question is from Hafa Fra
from city. You may proceed sir. You can
open your camera as well if you
want. Thank you. Good
morning. On the results
side, I see a very strong performance on
the revenue lines and I think Javanni
already talked a little bit about it,
but I would like to focus on the
provision expenses.
You talked about the recovery a few
times and that you still see room for
further improvement in terms of recovery
of write offs. But I would just like to
understand a little bit more about the
quality of the portfolio. All of the
lines presented a slight worsening in
NPL formation
uh maybe related to credit expectations
in in general. But I think that even if
we have minor worsenings in this NPL
formation, it's probably hard to see
that you will not you know over you know
you you would not go above the guidance.
I would like to understand why you had
that worsening and Juveni also mentioned
about the changes in the portfolio mix.
That came as a surprise to me because I
saw you know you know major changes in
the double A you know that was very fast
from one quarter to the next. So we
see some worsening on the NPL formation.
So can you explain how come you had this
improvement on recovery of writeoffs and
why at the same time you had worsening
in NPL formation? Well, Raphael, this is
Philippi. Philippe
Prince, thank you for your question.
First of all, there was not a
generalized worsening in the the lines
or a slight
worsening as we've been reporting
before.
Since the middle of last year, we had
applied a route correction in the
granting models of loans to
individuals. This proved to be very
assertive. And why am I speaking about
assertiveness? Because we we managed to
control credit granting to clients in
more risky lines and with the discipline
of Tarciana's execution. and she often
says that we were able to expand our
credit granting to clients with a better
risk
profile. Thus, you can notice that as
we've been saying as well, we reached
the peak of delinquency of individuals
in December. We
also deliver some reductions in the NPL
levels of individuals in this first
quarter. And it is precisely
these
dynamic
of transformation of this individual's
loan portfolio that is reflected in the
indicators you mentioned. So first of
all you have to mitigate the effect of
that specific
case where we migrate to all to
impairment in the coverage of this
new delinquency. So if you add these
amounts once again the amounts that were
migrated
our coverage is equivalent to what we've
been presenting in previous quarters.
So that's where we see 52 which in fact
would be 87. Therefore this is very much
in line with the risk profile of our
portfolio. And the migration as Javanni
said it himself is
predominantly linked to new originations
and risk profile of these
clients. Here we put great emphasis on
payroll loans.
As our co Taciana said, we've been very
aggressive also in terms
of granting loans to INSS pension
holders and this has strengthened our
portfolio which is now at much better
risk levels when compared to those of
2022 when in the first half we
incorporated that famous you know open
sea
vintage a bit more risky but all of the
models have been already adjusted and
they are performing quite well.
Therefore, we understand
that this was reflected in the numbers
of individuals NPL for 2023. And if I
could add, we are just going back to the
basics.
We know how to grant loans to our you
know bank account holders very well and
also we we are very strong in payroll
loans and payroll loans to INSS pension
holders and just like with other banks
everybody suffered struggled with with
delinquency in this line and this has
aggravated our provisions and not only
ours but everybody else's and we believe
that throughout the year this will be
diluted and we will be able to overcome
that
fact. In addition to that, you talked
about
collections. Yes, we
see
provisions, you know, going towards the
top of the guidance. Collection
performance was a bit worse in the first
quarter and especially in terms of
receivables through cash. We already
adjusted this strategy for the second
quarter. Therefore, what
we anticipate is that this will converge
to a level close to the top of the
credit risk in general. But we also have
the necessary tools to control
that. Perfect. If you allow me another
followup in in relation to your credit
book, your formation, NPO formation in
in individuals was slightly up and large
corporate was also slightly
up. Is this like a one-off situation? Do
you see that as a trend or you believe
that this will be maintained and then we
will probably see improvements
throughout the year? In terms of
individuals, this is a one-off
situation. It is right in the
convergence of the curves between, you
know, past originations and new
originations.
Well, on the corporate side, the
pressure is a bit higher because with
this current level of interest rates, we
have an additional pressure to the cash
flow companies and this is translated
into their payment capacity. In agri
business, we are in between crop
seasons. So naturally in the initial
months of the year, we see some
delinquency pressure. But we are just
talking about the lowest NPL indicator
if you look back in in our historical
series. Therefore, I can say that this
is a one-off situation. In terms of
trend, it's very much under control and
less severe in in terms of what the
market is delivering. And we attribute
that to to our capacity to operate in a
regional matter in productive chains in
also in segments that are linked to the
agrous chain. Therefore, we see that
there is a slight
tilt on the corporate side, but nothing
that points to any deterioration. On the
contrary, it's part of the business. And
we also see normal normalization of the
KPIs. They used to be very low since the
pandemic period and now we see in our
portfolio a corporate NPL that is
normalized. And as I said, we have a
very well-defined strategy to maintain
things under control. Great. Thank
you. Our next question comes from Ma
Mario Piri from Bank of
America. Good morning. Congratulations
on your results. My
question is on your NI.
Most part of this NI comes from treasury
and and treasury is benefiting from
increase in interest rates. Now when we
look at the margin as a
whole, treasury accounts for almost 50%
and historically that number was close
to
20%. How can you protect that
NI in in a landscape when interest rates
are falling? When we look
at client NI, it's growing alongside
with with credit. Is there any room for
repricing the portfolios? I mean,
considering a landscape in Brazil when
we see a tightening in credit, how do
you see the pricing of your products?
Hello, Mario. It's very good to see you
here. Well,
certainly we certainly have this concern
and we are already assessing the
possible impacts to our
NI once we we start a new cycle starting
the second half of the year when the
central bank starts reducing interest
rates. The fact is that for
us these reduction in interest rates
will help us in the funding cost because
we have a passive exposure postfixed. So
this will immediately favor the bank and
we also believe
that as this interest rate begins to
come down there will be repricing.
Therefore, looking at what is happening
now, there was a repricing on the asset
and credit sides, you know, at higher
rates. If you look at the rates in the
first quarter of 2022 versus 23, this
really explains the
increase on our revenue on the credit
size. And however, this also impacts
funding costs. But we were able to
improve the mix of our funding. And when
compared to other banks, we
have a mixture of funding coming from
savings accounts, you know, escro
deposits and in other areas where we
adopted some very specific approaches
and this allowed us to strengthen that
NII. looking forward, you know,
reductions in interest rates will have
an immediate effect, I mean positive
effect for us because this will reduce
our funding costs immediately. On the
other hand, this will allow for
repricing of the portfolios and also new
agreements. But for the time being, this
has been very positive to us. I think
that when we
look towards the future this would be
neutral for the margin for the
NI. So now
Javanni the idea is that you should be
able to
maintain your
uh a fi a stable NI regardless of the
interest rate scenario throughout the
year. we expect to be right within the
guidance line whe when you when you
compare to the same period of the year
before you you have that strategy that I
mentioned but we want to maintain it and
now we are already adopting other
measures to to be prepared within the
ALM logics to a new scenarios of lower
interest rates but we don't think that
it will be a hard landing will be a soft
landing
As the monetary authority starts
reducing this rate, the the Bank of
Brazil will be able to adapt the mix of
its assets and liabilities in order to
preserve the margin and also the result.
Great. Thank you.
Next
question by Danielle Vas with Ky
Swiss. Thank you Jenna. Congratulations
on the results. I'd like
to guide my question to what the
previous management said that the value
perception of Banko de Brazio was a
little deteriorated when we look at
valuation modles particularly in terms
of price earnings. We saw the bank very
discounted from the valuation that they
considered to be fair. Is this also the
opinion of the current management Tiana
and Giovannis? What are the measures
that you intend to adopt to increase the
valuation to a potential
rerating and think about what Giovenu
mentioned that you are adopting credit
measures to grow the portfolio with
quality and responsibility. Where do you
see that you are below your fair share
considering the market share of all
products? thinking about what could be
the focus. We saw in SS growing a lot.
What could be other uh possibilities of
growth? Thank you.
Thank you very much for the
question. I will start answering the
question. At the very
end, we understand that in some business
lines, the bank is well positioned to
have a more adequate
share, more adequate to our positioning
in payroll loans. We are leaders, but we
believe that we have
not gained the whole market share, a
fair market share. also in some business
lines. Again, I highlight INSS
loans and also payroll and deductible
loans in the private market. That's
another area where bank Brazil has an
opportunity to grow and gain market
share. Another business line is in auto
loans. That is a line where the bank is
operational but not at the same level as
other market players. So we understand
this is another segment loans for
automobiles where we can seek a fair
share for banko
Brazil. When we'll look at the every
business loans, we have room to regain
market share. Market share that used to
be ours. They used to be bankod Brazil's
and we have the right conditions to
increase at least 10 percentage points
and get 10 percentage points back in
that
segment. Given the volume of agri
business, perhaps this will not come in
2023. At least not at the pace that we
would like because it is a very big
portfolio. But these are profitable
business segments. These are safe
business segments and we know that we
have the right conditions to advance
there. And as regards your first
question, Daniel, undoubtedly the market
penalizes Bank of Brazil a
lot. It punishes us and there was I
shouldn't say panic, but the market was
perhaps using too heavy a hand to
discount bank of Brazil with the change
of the administration of the country.
But the truth is we are here. We are
relentless executing the same corporate
strategy that was
defined and the execution is the best
way to help the
market recover trust in the
bank. We are a management team formed by
current and former employees and
executives of the of Bank of Dubo
Brazio. We have a very bold agenda
to drive improvements,
digitalization, innovation, trying to be
closer and closer to our customers and
relevant to our customers, trying to
regain market share or gain market share
in some other
lines. When I left the bank in 2010, I
remember that one of the big pressures
by the government was little exposure
that Bank of Brazil had to individual
loans. which is what brings us more
margin and today our credit portfolio is
practically one/ird one third one third
in other words we walked the talk in
recent times and still the market
continues to punish us I don't think it
is related to operating performance of
bankodu Brazil or ability of our
management to execute the strategies but
due to other reasons that we are not
going to discuss here but we will
continue
tirelessly looking for ways to bring
adequate returns to all our
shareholders. We believe that uh a
return on equity of
21% does not justify the price that the
market is paying for Bank of
Brazil. Thank you for the answers. If I
can go back to Triciana's
answer, I only heard about a fair market
share for individuals and thinking about
corporate the corporate segment and the
companies. Do you think your fair share
um that you're below your fair share?
Can you expand this market or will you
be focusing on individuals
only? Danielle,
first I think that we have to underscore
what Joanni mentioned.
the strength of our mix that we pursued
on purpose and that we are delivering
now. One/ird oneird one third in the
large corporate segment. Our strategy
was very well defined and linked to
assisting our customers and origination
for the distribution of operations in
the capital markets strengthening our JV
with UBS.
The strategy was being very
successful. We were vice leaders in
several markets in
2022. However, there was one adverse
event that ended up freezing these
operations in
Q1. Now, dragging a little into
Q2. Now, of course, we try to maintain
assistance to our clients. They request
rollovers. They consume products and
services. And we always try to serve our
customers in a holistic way to serve
their
needs. So there is no appetite for us to
change the mix as it is.
There are some
circumstances that will lead us to
provide more assistance here and there,
more localized, but always thinking in
the future of distributing these
securities in the capital
markets. Perfect, Philippe. Thank you
very much. Thank you. Next question from
Eduardo Rosman with BTG.
Hello, good day everyone.
Congratulations on the results. I have
two follow-up questions regarding things
that
Giovani has mentioned in his last
answer. By the way, Giovanni, welcome
back. So, the first point is about ROE.
I think that well 21% ROE is very
strong. the capital has improved but it
seems that the market prices that are OE
will be dropping strongly in the coming
years. So I'd like to know is there any
reason for that to happen? We don't
think this is going to happen,
but do if you could give us some color
on what the ROE could be for the coming
years, it would be very useful. And you
talked about something nice that in 2010
when you left the bank, the market
wanted to buck to
Brazil to have more exposure to
individuals. And now that you're
back, what else do you think is
interesting in terms of things that have
changed that improved or things that as
an outsider you could see that there was
room for Bad Brazil to deliver and
improve? Thank you,
Roseman. I did not forget our
lunch. Fabiana has talked to me about
it. It's it's in my
calendar. All right. to answer your
questions.
Undoubtedly, people wonder how is it
possible that we are ending the results
of the financial sector
and and in a leading position in terms
of net income and
profitability and with a loan portfolio
that is superior to other banks. If we
look just at the Brazilian loan book
comparing with it when you were in their
international portfolio then there are
100 million ahead of us but undoubtedly
we have the calling to grant loans to
all sectors all lines. What is the
difference? We have greater
diversification. And if we look at the
degree of concentration per sector, we
will continue to do that. But more and
more what we are trying to do is do more
with less. So when I rejoined the bank,
what drew my attention was the cost to
income ratio. It was unimaginable. It
was a dream we had in 2010 to get to the
cost to income ratio that we currently
have at Bank of Brazil. And undoubtedly
a ratio of 29% the very best in our
history is just fantastic.
expense control which was another
problem. People talked about the
difficulty of bankodu in controlling our
expenses but we showed that yes we're
capable of controlling expenses
meanwhile continuing to play our role of
providing financing for all sectors of
the economy helping the country grow.
There's another point that draw
attention and you talked about it the
result of our strategic partnerships. It
is true that BB UBS specifically but the
market is closed for all all banks are
suffering including investment banks but
we've posted fantastic growth in
insurance which was the Achilles tendon
of the bank in the past. We grew
significantly our partnership with Elo.
If you look at the equity income result
you can see it. So we have a robust
structure to generate results in
financial intermediation in fee income
and we are not the most expensive bank.
We are not just a bank that charges fees
all the time from customers. What is
interesting to us is to be close to our
customers, be relevant to them,
increasing engagement with
them, building loyalty uh from our
customers. So today after 12 years being
away from Bankadoo Brazil I see a
different
company. If back then I was not ashamed
of being a bankad Brazil officer today
I'm even more proud. The market has to
stop with that
nonsense. The market needs to know how
to differentiate political issues
governance from governance and from
business topics. bunker to Brazil. Half
of its capital belongs to the
controlling shareholder, the federal
government government of Brazil. The
rest is in the hands of the market. It's
free float. This is the best private
public partnership there is as long as
it is well-managed and as long as it is
efficient and we are proving that yes,
we're capable of managing efficiently
delivering value to shareholders and
society. This is what gives us a
purpose. This is what makes our hearts
beat more strongly. Well, it's they
people say that the market is heartless.
I think that the market should recognize
that the heart of Makdrazi is beating
strong.
Shall we move on? Rosman, do you have
any follow-up questions?
No. No. Perfect.
Thank you very much for the answers and
we'll definitely schedule that lunch.
Thank you.
Our next question comes from
Haiki from Escat Bank.
Are you listening to us? Ah, you're in
the mute mode. What?
You're mute. No, we're not listening to
you.
No sound. Are you hear me? Yeah, now.
Yeah. Go on. Oh, okay. Perfect. Sorry
about that. Um,
so, uh, well, first, thank you for
taking my call and for the opportunity
to ask questions. Um, my question is
related to the cost to income ratio or
deficiency ratio.
We have seen a very strong levels as you
have previous previously mentioned. So I
am wondering looking forward what do you
think can be a more sustainable level?
Is is it going to be similar to what we
are seeing now or can we expect it to be
slightly higher? How should we think
about this going forward? Thank you. Uh,
thank you for the question, huh? Juan,
send send my my send my regard to uh
Jason Mullen. It's an old friend. I
would like to catch up with him later.
Okay. I'm going to switch to Portuguese
unfortunately so that everybody can hear
us. Okay. Uh,
certainly this is an efficiency level. I
mean this cost to income ratio makes us
very proud but it's also important to
bear in mind that this year as part of
our strategy to expedite the digital
side we already accommodated in our
budget to make further investments and
have further expenses to update our
technological hub and that's
why we can
expect a increase in our admin expense.
expenses around 8 or 9% which will be
close to our range of 7 to to 9%. And
this certainly will lead this cost to
income ratio to be slightly lower but we
will always struggle to be or fight to
be one of the most competitive banks
when compared to our peers. We believe
that being close to high 20s and low 30s
would
be perfectly
acceptable for us at Bankco Brazil.
Thank you.
Our next question is from Tito Laba from
Goldman Sachs.
Good to see you again a long time. Um my
my question following up I guess on
Rossman's question about ROE for the
bank and and also like on you know the
value for the bank. If you can help us
think a little bit how you think about
the long-term profitability for banker
Brazil and I say that within the context
of the banking system as well. Um I
think you know several moving things you
know you know the government has said
about using public sector banks to
support the economy to some extent. Um
you know if that were to happen what
potential impact could that have on
profitability and from the other
perspective you know we're
seeing fintexs and and digital banks you
know have grown a lot over the last 10
years and you know gaining share. How do
you see the impact of this sort of new
competitive environment and what
potential impact that can have on
profitability for the bank longer term?
Thank you. Hi Tito, nice seeing you.
Hope to catching up with you soon. Okay.
Well, um well, let me switch to
Portuguese. Sorry.
[Applause]
Uh what I believe
TU is that I mean we do
not release guidance on return on equity
but we believe that Banko Brazil is
perfectly capable of
delivering high tens and and low 20s in
this ROE
range while we remain very disciplined
in controlling our cost, protecting our
portfolio, growing loans with quality
and also improving the
hyperpersonalization mechanisms in terms
of our offers to our clients, increasing
their wallet of doing business with us.
While we do all that, we will be able to
protect the results of Banko de
Brazil. And much has been said about
public policies. Bank of the de Brazil
has been doing that for a long time
because this is part of our core
business and of our strategy. We are
constantly lending to the different
sectors of the economy l to our clients
because we are here to serve the needs
of our clients and that's why we need
you know as long as we have capital and
with a good funding base and as long as
we are competitive we will continue to
fulfill our role which is our vocation.
Now in relation to the competitive
environment there are certainly
regulatory issues involved and we are
very you know attentive to to them.
One example is the compliance to
Baso3 commercial practices and the
central bank itself has already decided
to postpone for another year the
requirement of capto use for operating
risk because this would impact the
entire industry. And certainly this
could be a burden not no longer for 2024
but maybe for
2026 as there will certainly be cons
more capital use from the banks to
comply with this new methodology of
calculation of operating risk within the
scope of uh
BIS3. Another issue has to do with the
competition from the newcomers or new
banks. And certainly I think that the
trend is towards a convergence or
accommodation of the rules for all
players
involved. These
are these are organizations that impact
means of payment and credit cards. But
bank of the Brazil has adopted very
specific strategies to protect his
market share and probably even to grow
in certain business lines that in the
past we were not very present or very
active and as an example I would like to
mention our investments in technology
and those investments will allow us to
be more
agile more digital and with
that we've managed to at least protect
our
base visav the new
entrance. I don't know Tariana whether
you would like to add anything else. So
basically,
Tito, we we believe that as the
landscape improves and interest rates
come down, we will see then a more
benign
scenario
to resume grow growth in the country and
the banks will be able to surf that wave
at a with a lower risk level. you
know in terms of also in terms of you
know capital use regarding the new BIS3
changes and one example is PICSS that TI
tariana mentioned I think we are the
largest processor of pix transactions
there are saying in Brazil that from the
lemon we can make a
lemonade all the analysts were concern
with the impact of from terrorists for
the banks with the introduction of PIX
transactions but we turn that quickly
into an opportunity to generate revenues
for the bank. Would you like to add
anything? Well, very briefly, but I
think you summarized it quite well. I
would just like to say that we we knew
how to protect our base quite well and
now you should expect that we are ready
to
attack. No comments to
add. Thank
you. Pedro.
Next question from Pedro
Leukaw. Hello. Thank you for the
opportunity to ask a question and
congratulations on the result. I have
two questions actually. One regarding
treasury
results what's called
interfinancial liquidity
investments. It was 16.5 billion the
last quarter dropping to 15 billion this
quarter. When we look at the balance of
these operations, it's just a result had
a decline and what do you call treasury
results? I'd like to understand why
there was some volatility in this uh
line which ended up driving down NII. So
these interfinancial liquidity
operations hurt a bit. That's my first
question. And my second question has to
do with
services formidable performance in all
lines. I'd like to hear from you
regarding current accounts increasing
five
six% year on year. Was there any
readjustment or what is the dynamic that
is sustaining this kind of growth? Thank
you very much.
Thank you Pedro for the question. I
don't know you personally but I hope to
meet you personally soon.
Pedro, in terms of treasury, it's
basically
um there's nothing worrisome there,
nothing to worry about. But what you're
going to see is that in the quarterly
comparisons, this will reflect
basically rates,
uh calendar
days, perhaps one specific funding
operation. So, there's nothing really
there to worry us.
We consider Treasury results as being
practically fat. Although flat I mean
although it it did show a little
decline. Q1 is a lazier quarter.
Everybody is on holidays but nothing to
worry about in our view. So rest
assured. I just want to make a comment
to Giovanni. This reduction there we saw
in liquidity Pedro is very marginal and
seasonal. Pedro, we understand that
treasury should stabilize close to this
level as we have more liquidity flowing
to credit. So you can see financial
revenue with credit operations growing
with the expansion of the loan book and
with a different mix. Thank you Jana.
Thank
you. And there was a question about the
current accounts and services.
Well, one of the factors that have
contributed to this is that we changed
the strategy from 2022 to 2023. We
changed the strategy of
Conteasio which was an entry-level
simplified checking account and we moved
it to full digital account. So the
profile of customers, the digital
profile of customers accessing the full
checking account is a profile of
customers that requires a more complete
portfolio of products and services. So
we have advanced in this entry door. The
current account is still an entry door
to the bank, but now we have customers
with a consumption profile that demand a
more complete portfolio. So this is
basically the change a strategy from an
easy checking account countasu to full
digital account important to say that we
didn't change the price and it is more
attractive a more attractive value
proposition without increasing the
price and with
accuracy. Next question from Nicholas Ha
with Bank of America.
chance to ask questions. Um, so I'm
going to ask on on the perpetual bonds.
Um, so last month you called the uh the
n and a quarters without any capital
replacement. You didn't come to market
at at the time and you know there is
quite a negative environment in the
market towards 81s in general after what
happened with great Swiss and the wipe
out of the 16 billion franks. Um so next
year you have to decide you still have
two uh perpetual bonds outstanding in
international market the the six and a
quarter and the nines um you have to
make a decision on the call next year
it's within two months of each other and
in total it's a very large amount in
total $4 billion or about 190 basis
points of 81. So my question is if for
the six and a quarters and the
nines you do believe that in order to
call them that you would need to replace
uh a good amount of of that that you
would need to come to market either in
the domestic or in the international
market and if there's a level a minimum
level of 81 capital that you would like
to to keep and um and also if you can
remind us your capital target I remember
uh the target of at least 11% C1 one but
if you can remind us about those targets
including if there is any targets for
tier one and for and for total capital.
Thanks. Hi Nicholas, thank you for the
question. That that that was definitely
my first task when I arrived here to to
how we're going to manage this $4
billion stars that we have next year for
April and June. So switching back to
Portuguese, uh
we still
evaluating what will be the best
solution that Bank Brazil will
adopt to address these two perpetual
bonds that have a window for call next
year. Unfortunately, this Criss episode
got in the way. We were considering to
tap this market
and to test also this market this year.
But undoubtedly it is a market that is
totally closed. Now we do accept
suggestions. If you want to send me an
email and make a suggestion and explain
your vision and how we could address it,
it would be great. But what I can say
publicly is that we are looking into
this. We are attentive and we will look
for the best solution that will add
value for the
company and we'll seek a solution that
will maintain a relationship open with
our
creditors, the best uh winwin
relationship for both parties. We are
sensitive to that. So much so that we
exercise the call recently. We know of
the importance
uh for the borrower of this bond. But we
also have to look at this from the
standpoint of Bangodu and our
shareholders and what is best for the
bank and shareholders. We're taking
everything into consideration and we are
open to market suggestions. Thank you
very
much Nicholas. Regarding the 11%
target, we had a target to be attained
as of 2019. We haven't got a new public
target, but at least this is the level
that we have declared in terms of CT
when we should not be far from market
average. And regarding capital
structure, oh yes, we lost the I will
repeat that to you. The target for I
will repeat that to you. Okay. Uh the
target back then was 11%. For now, we
don't have a public target. Okay, that
she said. Uh
can you hear me now? Nicholas. Well,
regarding capital
structure, we know that compared with
our peers, we are in a less leveraged
position. We have a CT level even
greater than our peers, believe it or
not.
But looking forward in the coming years,
we also have a hybrid instrument of
around 7 billion. This has been publicly
disclosed to the market and we have a
schedule of payments for that
uh paying back the controlling
shareholders. So all of these variables
are being
evaluated so that we can project what
would be the best optimal capital
structure for Bankadoo Brazil
considering expectation of credit
growth, expected reduction of interest
rates, the possibility of getting
funding in the market, exercising
possibly the call or eventually
resetting interest rates of
per
So you can see I have a big homework to
do that Tarsiano gave me to evaluate
this because time is
short. Our next question is for from
Carlos Gomez Lopez from
HSBC. Hello Janaya Taciana and Giovanni.
It's nice to see you again.
My
question is about your growth outlook
for the coming
years. What do you
believe would be the growth of Beno
Brazil for the next 3 to four years? And
having said
that, if you have a lower growth than
the one you have now of
15%. Do you think that you could grow
above that or not?
Carlos was with us since the first
offering we did way back then was still
on the buy
side. Carlos I mean this is a difficult
question. Our strategy has been defined
to up to 2027. Right. Yes. But there are
variables that throughout this period
until 2027
uh will have to be well managed. The
federal government is designing a
program aimed
at
renegotiating households household debt.
And this gives room to increase in loans
in the individual's
portfolio as the bond
market resumes
growth and allows
for funding to large corporate be
through private bonds. I would say that
right now it's very difficult for me to
give you a growth rate for the long run
a long run um growth rate in
our loan portfolio but I would say that
is perfectly sustainable considering our
capital structure and our funding base
it would be good to it would be
advisable to maintain something around 9
to 12% maybe within that range we will
be able to to work
without without making many mistakes. Of
course, we want to take advantage of the
opportunities that the market will
offer. But looking at the loan book as a
whole and also considering that we are a
major player in terms of providing loans
to every business, we will probably be
close to low
tens or close to nine depending on the
other lines.
So you're talking about capital if
you're saying nine or
11%.
So you would grow more on mortgage loans
too. I so I think you you be probably
delivering more than the 40% you're
delivering today. Yeah. Our commitment
is for a payout of 40%. I'm not going to
be committed to pay anything more than
that. But once we are more profitable
when compared to what is available for
our investors to invest, I think it's
it's worth it keeping the money in house
because we can take very good care of
it. Giovanni, I think we still have some
regulatory homework to do in Brazil.
So we have to deliver IFRS9 until
2025. We are in an advanced phase of
adaptation. But certainly this may lead
to some sort of capital use and as
Giovanni said before BIS 3 phase 2 that
impacts has an impact on operating risk
and this could lead to capital
indicators could have an impact on risk
indicators. What I can tell you is that
none of these
moves are capable of removing our
leverage capacity and also our capacity
to fulfill our commitment to pay out 40%
of dividends. And you know it will all
depend on our execution discipline and
certainly on the effect of all of these
new regulatory
demands.
Could you give me an initial estimate on
the impact of the largest operating
risk? We are working with a range of
around 100 beeps
bps. Now moving towards the end of our
conference call, our last question will
be from Philip Navahu from Santandere.
Thank you, Janina, and congratulations
on your results. Giovanni, it's good to
see you
back. Like good old days. Bank of Brazil
is one of the very few banks
that discloses figures on uh credit card
delinquency. This quarter, after several
previous quarters, there was a drastic
drop in NPL from credit cards.
My question is I mean I would like to
use the data and market intelligence
from Bank of Brazil to help me
understand what's happening with the
industry. Could we say that this drop is
a structural or is part of the financial
system or that was probably due to your
well done homework and also going
forward the credit card market. Do you
think it still requires caution? Should
we look forward and see this delinquency
level coming down even further? That's
it. I just want to get a better
understanding of how the market behaves.
Nahu, it's very good to see you. I hope
I can see you in person very
soon. I think that Prince can give you
some more
color. Thank you, Javanni. And our
president Tariana was an active part of
that movement. We understand that this
is a movement from Banko to Brazil
alone. We looked at the initial vintages
of 2022 and we saw a deterioration in
credit card granting
particularly related to the open sea
lines. There was our digital credit card
that we call autoart card fasio. We made
adjustments to the models back in the
middle of last year and that adjustment
was progressive. So why do I think that
we deliver a different situation when
compared to the rest of the market? Even
if you look at figures from Bank of
Brazil, I mean to the the credit market,
delinquency credit card continues to
grow. If you look at the overall market,
but looking at bankod to Brazil's
figures, we should see the peak in
December and from then on we will
reverse the curve starting the first
quarter. And that's what you can tell if
you look at our data. We are one of the
only large banks that have a very
detailed disclosure of this figures. So
this is attributed to a strategy to
control
risk that client
profile that was posting stronger
deterioration
indicators.
But at the same time, we motivated the
granting to our customer base
that didn't use credit cards as much
when compared to the average credit card
use amongst our other clients. We try to
foster the centralization of the
invoices in the bank. We were very
proactive. We started by identifying the
profile of clients. We evaluated their
expenditures, their behavior and also
all of that linked to risk and this
was was submitted to our negotiation
desks in our branches in order for us to
attract clients with better consumption
profiles. Then you even mentioned this
drop in the first quarter. We don't call
it a drop
because seasonality plays a part here
because we have you know Black Friday
and the Christmas
holidays. The performance in terms of
volume in the fourth quarter cannot be
compared to any other quarter of the
year. So we understand that there was a
favorable performance in terms of the
portfolio in the first quarter and this
is attributed to a very welldefined
strategy with a disciplined execution
which is being required by our CEO
Tarcia and that's why we were able to
deliver those numbers but the market
trend is quite
different Navahu. I would just like to
add a few more comments to what Philippe
Prince said. We are looking at the
behavioral patterns of our customers
because we want to deliver a bank for
each client and this is a case of the
bank. Not only we are careful enough so
that the new vintages and the new
product
entries are such that a client that fits
the profile for the product is suitable
for the product but also we look at the
client's demand because maybe that
demand was for another credit line. So
we just migrated the client to its
adequate uh credit line according to its
payment capacity or debt capacity. This
development of models that are more
knowledgeable about clients is very
helpful because it's important that we
offer the right products to our clients
based on their consumption patterns. And
we also help
them and guide them through the
adequate caps on the credit
card amount. And so this result stems
from this very articulated work on the
part of the bank. We did our homework
and we intend to, you know, to keep
going with that. Thank you very much.
Very well then we're ending the Q&A
session and to close I'd like to turn
the floor to our CEO Tristiana for her
final statements. Well, I'd like to
thank
everyone for your
questions. Thank you very much for your
partnership, for being close to us on a
day today.
will always be available to speak with
you
to clear all your
doubts so that our shares can have a
fair price in the market. So count on us
because we definitely count on you.
Thank you very much and I'll see you
next
time. Thank you.